missionmainstreetgrants.com 2015-12-04

# Privacy Policy Mission Main Street Grants® 2015 | Mission Main Street Grants ®

This privacy policy (“Policy”) is intended to help you understand how Chase (or “we”) may collect and use information about you in connection with the Mission Main Street Grants Program (“MMSG Program”) and the MMSG Program website (the “MMSG Site”). If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, which supplements the MMSG Program Rules, please do not use the MMSG Site. 

_**Information we collect:**_ Chase will collect any information you provide directly to Chase on the MMSG Site such as an e-mail address as well as any information you give us permission to collect through connections with other websites (e.g., LinkedIn). For example, when you set up your Account, your Business Profile or submit the Grant Questionnaire (collectively, the “MMSG Application”), Chase will collect and have access to the information that you provide, some of which may be personal information. In addition, if you choose to vote using Facebook, we may be given access to, and store, your Facebook profile identification number and other information that Facebook makes available to facilitate the voting process. 

_**Usage Information:**_ When you use the MMSG Site, our servers automatically capture information like your IP address and other unique identifiers for the computer or device you are using. We may also capture certain “clickstream data” such as the operating system and Web browser you use to access the MMSG Site, the referring page that linked you to the MMSG Site, the pages you visit within the MMSG Site, and the next Web site you visit when you leave the MMSG Site. 

_**Cookies and other Tracking Technologies:**_ We, and others acting on our behalf, may deploy cookies, local shared objects, pixel tags and other tracking technologies through the MMSG Site to collect information about you or your visits. These tracking technologies help us to better understand our audience and the ways in which the MMSG Site is used. They may also help us enhance your experience with the MMSG Site. By using the MMSG Site, you agree to our use of these tracking technologies. 

_**Use of information:**_ Chase will use the information it collects to administer and communicate with you regarding the MMSG programs available through the MMSG Site and other Chase programs. For example, your Facebook profile identification number is used to identify you when you visit the MMSG Site so that we can provide you access to the MMSG Program functionality. 

_**Sharing of information:**_ Chase may share the information collected through the MMSG Site in a variety of circumstances. For example, we may share information: 

  * with those who need your information in order to help us provide the MMSG Program and other Chase programs and services
  * when you voluntarily post content to public areas of the MMSG Site
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or property, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a government, judicial or other legal request
  * in connection with a corporate change including a merger, acquisition, reorganization, consolidation, liquidation, or sale of assets

Nothing herein restricts the sharing of information we collect from you in an aggregated or anonymized form that does not directly identify you, and such information may be shared in any manner and for any purpose without your consent. This can include usage information that is not connected to personal information. 

_**Links to Other Websites:**_ The MMSG Site may contain links to other websites. This Policy does not apply to such linked sites, and we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of these websites. We encourage you to learn about the privacy and security practices of the websites you visit before providing any personal information. 

_**Changes to this Policy:**_ We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the Policy the date it was last updated. 

_**Miscellaneous:**_ Chase makes no representation that the Policy and our practices comply with laws outside of the United States. Visitors who use the MMSG Site and reside outside of the United States do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. If you reside outside of the United States, by using the MMSG Site, you consent to the transfer, processing and use of your information outside of your country. 

_**How to contact Chase:**_ If you wish to contact us in regard to the MMSG Program, you can do so by sending an email through the CONTACT US link on the MMSG Site. 

JPMorgan Chase Bank, N.A.May 4, 2015
